Guide to the Women's Veterinary Circle records, 1925-1994
Women's Veterinary Circle records, 1925-1994
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Women's Veterinary Circle records 1925-1994
11-8-3046
Women's Veterinary Circle
0.7 cubic ft.
Minutes, membership lists, and publicity files.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Minutes, membership lists, and publicity about the Women's Veterinary Circle. Also includes newsletters and other material relating to the Women's Auxiliary of the American Veterinary Medical Association, its junior and student chapters.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Informal social group of New York State Veterinary College faculty and graduate student wives. The collection was assembled by Edith M. Poppensiek who was active in the organization during the tenure of G. C. Poppensiek as Dean of the College.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Minutes, membership lists, and publicity about the group, including typewritten and manuscript records kept by the group's secretary and treasurer. Also includes newsletters and other material relating to the Women's Auxiliary of the American Veterinary Medical Association, its junior and student chapters.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Women's Veterinary Circle.; American Veterinary Medical Association. Women's Auxiliary.; American Veterinary Medical Association. Cornell University Student Chapter.; New York State Veterinary College.; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine.
Subjects:
Women--New York (State)--Ithaca--Societies and clubs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
The New York State Veterinary Medical Society Auxiliary records RMC # 6600
Veterinary Student Wives records RMC # 52-1-3384
CONTAINER LIST
- Auxiliary history (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Auxiliary newsletters, ca. 1967, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Auxiliary directories, 1964-1974 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Auxiliary constitution, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Auxiliary directories, 1959-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Auxiliary annual reports, 1961-1972 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Brochures, programs, ca. 1970's-1980's (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Misc. (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Honor Code of NYS Vet. College, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Vet. Circle committees, events and directories, 1962-1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Vet. Circle committees, events and directories, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Vet. Circle committees, events and directories, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Vet. Circle committees, events and directories, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Vet. Circle committees, events and directories, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Vet. Circle committees, events and directories, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Vet. Circle committees, events and directories, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Vet. Circle committees, events and directories, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Vet. Circle committees, events and directories, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Vet. Circle committees, events and directories, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Vet. Circle committees, events and directories, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Vet. Circle Secretary and Treasurer's records, 1925-1938 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Vet. Circle record book, 1925-1944 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Vet. Circle record book, ca. 1987-1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Vet. Circle minutes, programs, etc., 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Vet. Circle conference info, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)